You may have noticed that your
health insurance premium is
increasing regularly, and you might be wondering
why. Let's discuss the reasons as you
read on. Medical expenses
affect health insurance premiums.
Doctors' fees are rising almost every year.
Medicines are becoming more expensive. Medical
technology is improving. To
combat this, many health
insurers have steep price increases,
which can lead to a
significant jump in premiums when you switch banks. However,
we believe that a
gradual increase every year is a better approach
so that you don't face a sudden financial burden.
As we age,
our expenses for maintaining our health
increase. We ensure that
our customers understand the health risks involved at a young age rather than having to
pay a higher premium. To be a
trusted health insurance partner,
being there during the toughest times is paramount.
Max Bupa ensures
that every single one of your genuine claims is paid.
Our 30-minute cashless claims process
promise means we'll be there when you need us most. So,
finally, if you pay
attention to the important fact, you can put your mind at ease.  Regular increases are just a small payment for the peace
and well-being of you and your family